all right well I welcome everybody glad
好吧，我欢迎大家高兴
that you could all make it looking I see
你们都可以让它看起来像
a few familiar faces out there us ooh my
一些熟悉的面孔，我们哦，我的
son for coming
儿子要来
so today yeah I'm sure you've seen the
所以今天是的，我确定你已经看过
safe harbor statement a whole bunch of
安全港声明一大堆
times but I kind of just want to
时代，但我只是想
re-emphasize it for this talk because
在本次演讲中再次强调
everything I'm talking about in today's
我今天谈论的一切
section or today's session is
本节或今天的会议是
experimental as of JDK 9 and not
从JDK 9开始试验性的
officially supported in any way so
以任何方式得到官方支持
usually we just kind of pass right
通常我们只是通过
through these things but in this case it
通过这些事情，但在这种情况下
actually is kind of important so please
其实很重要，所以请
don't build your entire production
不要建立整个产品
system based off of the OT technology
基于OT技术的系统
you're gonna talk we're going to talk
你要说我们要说
about today so a few people in the
今天大约有几个人
audience I think know me but just for
听众，我想知道我，但只是为了
those of you who don't I'm a JVM
那些不属于我的人
sustaining engineer which means I fix
持续的工程师，这意味着我要修复
post release hotspot bugs that's my day
这是我今天发布的热点错误
job I'm almost of the JDK updates
我几乎是JDK更新的工作
project maintainer or one of them so you
项目维护者或其中之一，所以您
can find me sometimes arguing with
有时会找我吵架
people online about what kind of changes
网上人们关于什么样的变化
should and shouldn't make it into update
应该也不应更新
releases I've done Java one before
发布我之前做过Java的版本
I'm co-author of Japan's best-selling
我是日本最畅销书的合著者
WebLogic book and I do Twitter and have
WebLogic书，我做Twitter，有
a blog so we don't have a whole lot of
一个博客，所以我们没有很多
time to talk today so we're gonna kind
今天要谈谈，所以我们会很友善
of try and keep things fairly simple
尝试使事情保持简单
this is one of three different IOT talks
这是三种不同的物联网讨论之一
that I'm aware of
我知道的
at JavaOne this week and fortunately the
本周在JavaOne上，幸运的是
other two talks are all tomorrow so if
其他两个谈话都是明天，所以如果
you weren't planning on necessarily
你并没有计划
attending them tomorrow maybe you can a
明天参加他们也许你可以
put that into your schedule because some
把它放在你的时间表，因为一些
of the upcoming talks look pretty
即将举行的演讲看起来很漂亮
interesting and good too and I have some
有趣又好，我有一些
pointers to them at the end of the slide
幻灯片末尾指向它们的指针
deck but for day this is kind of an
甲板上，但今天这有点像
introduction to the feature itself we're
功能本身介绍
gonna start off at the very beginning
一开始就要开始
and kind of introduce what IOT is and
并介绍什么是物联网
what the goals are that kind of the
这样的目标是什么
design goals for this new feature and
此新功能的设计目标以及
what you might hope to get out of it so
您可能希望摆脱它的原因
we start off with some kind of boring
我们从某种无聊开始
warnings just to make sure that there's
警告只是为了确保有
no misunderstanding and that everyone
没有误会，每个人
takes everything I say with a little bit
一点点地接受我说的一切
of grain of salt so the first thing is
盐粒，所以第一件事是
that like I said before it's not yet
就像我之前说过的那样
officially supported son and then later
正式支持儿子，然后再
Oracle kinda has a long history of
Oracle有点悠久的历史
introducing new features this way other
通过其他方式介绍新功能
examples might be tiered compilation
示例可能是分层编译
the gg1 compiler the car I'm the the g1
gg1编译器我是g1车
garbage collector garbage first these
垃圾收集器首先这些垃圾
are all features that originally enter
是最初输入的所有功能
the product as an experimental feature
产品作为实验功能
that was not officially supported and
没有得到官方的支持，
then they became supported and then
然后他们得到了支持，然后
later they became the default enabled
后来他们成为默认启用
right out of the box and so while we
开箱即用，所以当我们
don't know for sure whether whether a OT
不确定是否有OT
will will take a similar path there
那里会走类似的路
there is kind of room for optimism but
有种乐观的空间，但是
as of now it's not something that you
到现在为止，这还不是你
can really affect expect official
真的可以影响期望官方
support from Oracle from that said if
从甲骨文的支持说，如果
you do find a bug please file a bug
您确实发现错误，请提交错误
report we want to know about them we
报告我们想了解他们，我们
want to fix it we want to make this as
要修复它，我们要使其成为
high quality as possible as of today
到今天为止尽可能高质量
it's only supported on Intel 64-bit for
仅在Intel 64位上支持
pro Linux and also just as another
专业Linux，以及其他
requirement you have to have lib e.l.f
要求您必须拥有lib elf
installed that's no biggie you just have
安装好了，这没什么大不了的
to get it before you build or whatever
在建造之前获得它
but it has to be there and so hopefully
但它必须在那里，所以希望
we're planning on adding other other
我们正计划添加其他
platforms as well in the future but for
平台以及将来
today this is the only one that you can
今天，这是你唯一可以
use this on there's also no official
没有官方使用
documentation which hopefully I'll kind
希望我能帮忙的文档
of fill the gap a little bit with
填补与
today's session the only official thing
今天的会议是唯一的官方事情
out there really is is the jep document
外面确实是jep文件
and again there right now we don't know
再一次，现在我们不知道
when or even if official support will
何时甚至即使官方支持
follow or in what timeframe certain
遵循或确定在什么时间范围内
platforms may or may not be entered
平台可能会或可能不会输入
that's all the boring boilerplate I had
这就是我所有无聊的样板
to get out of the way let's let's
为了摆脱困境，让我们
actually jump into a ot and what it's
实际上跳入一个OT，它是什么
all about
所有关于
so given all the the things I just said
鉴于我刚才说的所有话
why would you bother learning about it
你为什么要去学习
if you can't you know really use it in
如果您不知道是否真的在使用它
production yet well for one thing it's
生产还不错，这是一件事
pretty darn likely that this may be
很有可能这可能是
supported in the future and so just in
在将来得到支持，所以就在
the same sense that you want to get a
您想要获得相同的感觉
hold of EA builds early access builds
持有EA版本和早期访问版本
and play with them to learn about the
和他们一起玩以了解
direction the platform may go in on this
平台可能会在此方向
is your opportunity to get a jumpstart
是您获得快速入门的机会
on on what may be a very important and
关于什么可能是非常重要的
exciting technology being introduced to
令人兴奋的技术被引入
the platform the other thing is that
在平台上另一件事是
like most of my talks we're going to
像我的大多数演讲一样，我们将
jump off on a few random tangents that
跳上一些随机的切线
brush up against other features of the
克服其他功能
hotspot JVM and
热点JVM和
so it's kind of a good excuse to just
所以这是一个很好的借口
kind of cover some interesting material
覆盖一些有趣的材料
and also if you're anything like me you
而且如果你像我一样
just think this stuff is really cool and
只是觉得这东西真的很酷，
a whole lot of fun so it's always good
很有趣，所以总是很好
to kind of explore and get a peek under
进行探索并窥视
the hood so everyone's really interested
引擎盖，所以每个人都很感兴趣
in this because this is a fundamental
因为这是根本
change or addition to Javas execution
更改或添加Java执行
model and that's been kind of in place
模型，并且已经存在
since the beginning of time immortal so
自从不朽之始
originally we had you know you had your
原来我们有你知道你有你的
java source code you can pile to Java C
您可以堆放在Java C上的Java源代码
you get a class file and then you run
您得到一个类文件，然后运行
that on the runtime this should not be
在运行时这不应该是
surprising to anyone and then of course
让任何人都感到惊讶，然后当然
in the the java 1.2 time frame we
在Java 1.2时间框架中
started adding JIT compilation into the
开始将JIT编译添加到
mix and so while you were running your
混合，所以在您运行时
application on your runtime the JIT
JIT上运行应用程序
compiler would emit actual machine code
编译器将发出实际的机器代码
that would be stored and run from memory
将被存储并从内存中运行
and JIT compilation has many advantages
JIT编译有很多优点
the idea here is that methods do get
这里的想法是方法确实可以
compiled but compilation is expensive
编译但是编译很昂贵
compilation is always a very resource
编译总是很资源
intensive exercise and so both CPU
激烈的运动，因此CPU
cycles and memory are being consumed and
周期和内存被消耗，
your applications execution threads are
您的应用程序执行线程是
basically competing with the C 1 and C 2
基本上与C 1和C 2竞争
compilation threads for limited
有限的编译线程
resources or finite resources in your
您的资源或有限资源
application but once we do get over that
应用程序，但是一旦我们克服了
hump and we get the method compiled the
驼峰，我们得到编译的方法
machine language versions that we admit
我们承认的机器语言版本
run very very fast and gives us the peak
运行非常非常快，使我们达到了顶峰
performance that we expect from Java
我们期望从Java获得的性能
today but one reasonable question is is
今天，一个合理的问题是
well is j compilation really always
好吧，j编译真的总是
superior or better than just peer
优于或优于同龄人
interpolate in a peer interpreter
插入同声传译器
implementation and we kind of have as a
实施，我们有点像
possible case study of that J rocket so
该J火箭的可能案例研究
I didn't mention in my self introduction
我在自我介绍中没有提到
but I actually come from from the J
但我实际上来自J
rocket side of things originally and we
事情原本是火箭的一面，我们
had a pure jet what kind of like a
拥有纯净的喷气式飞机
classic jet implementation where we
经典喷气式飞机的实现方式
didn't have an interpreter like hotspot
没有像热点这样的口译员
does to fall back on so everything just
确实要依靠，所以一切都只是
got jet compiled by default and so does
默认情况下对jet进行了编译，所以
this really give you better performance
这确实给你更好的表现
this kind of of militantly trying to
这种好战的尝试
everything to machine code and the
一切机器代码和
answer is well what's your definition of
答案很好，你对它的定义是什么
performance so kind of an extreme
性能如此极端
example and no this is profoundly unfair
例子，没有，这是非常不公平的
to Java but on left here I'm running
Java，但在这里我正在运行
just a native HelloWorld you know that
只是本地的HelloWorld，您知道
was written in C you know this this
用C写的，你知道这个
comparison means nothing because
比较毫无意义，因为
obviously something written like that
显然是这样写的
versus a full runtime of garbage
而不是整个运行时的垃圾
collection and everything else Java
集合和其他所有Java
brings to the table
带到桌子上
you're not going to compete but the idea
你不会竞争而是这个想法
here is that that people really do look
这是人们真的看起来
at this these types of use cases and are
在这些类型的用例中，
asking themselves you know like like
问自己你知道像
well why does Java take so long so
好吧，为什么Java需要这么长时间
there's always been this this pressure
总是有这种压力
to try and make Java start up and run as
尝试使Java启动并以
fast as possible and so the point of
尽可能快，所以重点
using HelloWorld here is that just out
在这里使用HelloWorld就是
of the box even executing anything you
甚至执行任何操作
know the JVM is kind of behind the
知道JVM有点落后
native world in terms of startup time
在启动时间方面的原生世界
and people noticed that and so whether
人们注意到了
the comparison is fair or not people
比较公平与否
make that comparison and it's something
做比较，这是东西
that that we have to be aware of and and
我们必须意识到的
that kind of motivates us to try and
这种动机促使我们尝试
prove on these times as much as humanly
在这些时间上证明与人类一样多
possible so check compilation isn't
可能，所以检查编译不是
always fastest and that's why we have
总是最快，这就是为什么我们有
the hotspot way of thinking or
热点思维方式或
philosophy where we don't J compile
我们不J编译的哲学
everything like J rocket did
像J火箭所做的一切
so like I said the couple the overhead
就像我说的，这对夫妻开销
for compilation is is extremely high and
编译非常高
so we're consuming resources like memory
所以我们正在消耗内存等资源
and CPU time but also another issue that
和CPU时间，还有另一个问题
people are not necessarily always aware
人们不一定总是意识到
of is that there's also a latency
的是还有延迟
involved with JIT compilation and what I
参与JIT编译以及我的工作
mean by that is that even though we have
意思是即使我们有
the interpreter that can can start
可以开始的口译员
running the code immediately and we can
立即运行代码，我们可以
asynchronously do the the compilation
异步进行编译
and a separate compilation thread there
还有一个单独的编译线程
there's a delay before we get that
我们有一个延迟
compiled version so there's a delay
编译版本，因此会有延迟
before we hit the peak performance for
在我们达到最佳性能之前
that particular method and so in the
那个特定的方法等等
sense you know we get to run it
感觉你知道我们可以运行它
immediately but we're running it slow
立即，但我们运行缓慢
we're running it in the interpreter and
我们在解释器中运行它，
what we want to be doing is we want to
我们想要做的是我们想要
be running it the fastest version of
运行它的最快版本
that method the compiled version of that
该方法的编译版本
method as fast as humanly possible
尽可能快的方法
so in hotspot what we do is we start off
所以在热点，我们要做的是开始
every method begins with being
每种方法都始于
interpreted that's the default you know
解释这是你知道的默认值
behavior that everything gets and then
一切都会发生的行为，然后
we're constantly doing what we call
我们一直在做我们所谓的
hotspot profiling which is basically
热点分析基本上是
just collecting you know doing a stop
只是收集你知道停下来
the world and seeing what all the
世界，看到所有
threads are running and keeping track of
线程正在运行并跟踪
all that and then we have statistics for
所有这些，然后我们有统计
for you know invocation counts and
因为您知道调用计数和
things like that
像这样的东西
the interpreter actually gives us most
口译员实际上给了我们最多
of that information for free anyway so
无论如何都是免费的
we have all this information and then we
我们拥有所有这些信息，然后我们
identify which methods are high and we
确定哪些方法是高方法，我们
only just compiled those and then the
只是编译那些，然后
interpreted ones just remain interpreted
解释的只是保持解释
you know so things like static
你知道静态之类的东西
initializers and and other stuff that
初始化程序和其他东西
you know just there's no value in paying
你知道支付毫无价值
the overhead cost of compiling we just
编译的间接费用只是
avoid by compiling by not compiling at
通过不编译来避免
all but even with hotspots JIT that
除了热点JIT，
there's still some some very bad kind of
还有一些很糟糕的
weak points that that we have to deal
我们必须解决的弱点
with application startup time is still
与应用程序启动时间仍然
an issue it takes you know longer we
一个问题需要你知道我们更长的时间
have a warmup period so even after your
有一个热身期，所以即使你
application starts responding to
应用程序开始响应
incoming requests it still may take a
传入的请求仍然可能需要一个
while before enough of the hot methods
在足够的热门方法之前
get compiled to machine code and we
得到编译为机器代码，我们
start seeing peak performance so startup
开始看到最佳性能，因此启动
time is one measure and then time to
时间是一种度量，然后是时间
peak performance is another measure and
最佳表现是另一项指标，
they're both things where there's
他们俩都是
possible room for improvement in the
可能的改进空间
current compilation model and again
当前的编译模型
we're consuming a lot of resources most
我们最消耗大量资源
notably memory and as kind of a side
尤其是记忆力和某种方面
thing not so much of an issue with
事情不是什么大问题
Oracle's product offerings but there are
甲骨文的产品，但有
some platforms out there that for
一些平台
whatever reason disallow the dynamic
出于任何原因不允许动态
generation of machine code at runtime
在运行时生成机器代码
and so if you wanted to run the JVM on
因此，如果您想在
them you're kind of stuck with an
他们你有点被困在
interpreter unless you can find some way
解释器，除非您能找到一些方法
around that so this is something I
围绕着这就是我
talked I talked about him yes in my
我在我谈论过他
session yesterday and I think those
昨天的会议，我认为那些
people are there with us but there's two
人们和我们在一起，但有两个
separate compilers that are built into
内置的独立编译器
the hot spot a VM a c1 which is for
虚拟机a c1的热点
client use which kind of just does a
客户使用哪种类型的
quick and dirty compilation the idea is
快速而肮脏的编译的想法是
to kind of finish the act of compiling
完成某种编辑行为
and get that that quicker machine
得到那台更快的机器
language version of the method available
该方法的语言版本
for execution as fast as possible then
为了尽快执行
there's C 2 which is the server compiler
C 2是服务器编译器
and that one spends a lot more time
那会花很多时间
ie resources on on doing very heavy
即资源做得很重
optimization to give you the most
优化以给您最大的收益
performant code as possible and that one
尽可能的高性能代码
of the key differences here is that c2
这里的关键区别是c2
can't just run out of the blue c2
不能只用完C2
depends on having a whole bunch of
取决于有一堆
profiling data that was collected by the
分析由收集的数据
runtime before it compiles a method and
编译方法之前的运行时
so without that data we can't really see
因此，没有这些数据，我们将无法真正看到
to compile methods and that will come
编译方法，这将会
into play later and in a few more slides
稍后再播放
so that's the current situation as it
这就是目前的情况
exists kind of today or before JDK 9 so
存在于今天或JDK 9之前
what does a Oh to bring a ot bringing to
哦，要带给别人带什么？
the table here well the idea is of
这里的桌子很好的想法是
course you know because it's ahead of
你当然知道，因为它领先
time is to generate machine code before
时间是在生成机器代码之前
the runtime before we actually run the
我们实际运行之前的运行时
application so this is kind of just like
应用程序，所以这就像
like traditional static compilation and
像传统的静态编译和
so the JVM hopefully can find and load
因此JVM有望找到并加载
that code during runtime and then we
该代码在运行时，然后我们
bypass the latency in the overhead of
绕过系统开销的延迟
compilation work while we're running so
在我们运行的同时进行编译工作
this is the the kind of standard model
这是一种标准模型
that we have today again we just saw
今天又有了，我们刚刚看到
this in a slide a few slides ago and the
在几张幻灯片中的幻灯片中，
the addition here is that now we have
另外，现在我们有了
this new tool this.j a OTC Java ahead of
这个新工具this.ja OTC Java领先于
time compiler and it's going to give you
时间编译器，它将为您提供
an e LF shared object or shared library
LF共享对象或共享库
that you can load into the runtime and
您可以加载到运行时
use that pre-existing machine code to
使用该预先存在的机器代码来
startup as fast as possible but there's
尽快启动，但是有
some other benefits here and so in a
这里有一些其他好处，所以在
traditional model where you have
您拥有的传统模型
multiple JVM running and they're all
多个JVM在运行，它们都是
running the same code like say some sort
运行相同的代码，例如说某种
of of redundancy or clustering we've
冗余或集群
been the same OS VM you each JVM kind of
是每个JVM都使用的同一OS VM
gets its own copy of it so not only
得到它自己的副本，所以不仅
you're paying the performance cost of
您要支付的性能费用
compiling it all those times but then
所有这些时间都进行编译，但随后
once you have the output of that act of
一旦你有该行为的输出
compilation once you have the actual
一旦有了实际的编译
machine code that has to be kept in the
必须保留在机器代码中
code cache and the code cache takes up a
代码缓存，代码缓存占用一个
lot of space especially with the
很大的空间，尤其是
introduction of tiered compilation our
介绍分层编译
code cache size expanded by about five
代码缓存大小扩大了大约五倍
times and so if you run a lot of JVMs on
时间，所以如果您在上运行很多JVM
the same OS instance
同一操作系统实例
that can actually be a lot of
实际上可能很多
unnecessary redundant overhead so t
不必要的冗余开销
allows us to create these read-only
允许我们创建这些只读
segments in memory that have the the
内存中具有
machine code in them and the commission
其中的机器代码和佣金
that can be shared across multiple JVM
可以在多个JVM之间共享
instances and so we have a density
实例，所以我们有一个密度
improvement where if you're deploying
如果您要部署的地方进行改进
all these different gems to the cloud
所有这些不同的宝石云
the total consumed memory is going to be
总消耗的内存将是
less so there's a lot of advantages here
少，所以这里有很多优点
it's going to give you faster startup
它可以使您更快地启动
times this this is just you know as soon
时代这只是你知道
as your your application is ready to
当您的应用程序准备好
start actually taking and processing
开始实际服用和加工
requests that's going to improve then we
要求将有所改善，然后我们
have beyond that faster warmup times or
具有更快的预热时间或
less warmup time and so even though it's
预热时间更少，因此即使
taking requests like I said a few slides
像我说几张幻灯片一样接受请求
earlier it takes a little while before
之前需要一段时间
you reach peak performance but with t
您可以达到最佳性能，但是
because a lot of that those hot methods
因为很多那些热门方法
are already going to be available we can
已经可以使用了
reach peak performance much faster and
更快达到最佳性能，
of course because we're not doing that
当然是因为我们没有这样做
compilation at runtime we also have less
在运行时进行编译，我们也减少了
memory footprint we have a less overhead
内存占用量，我们的开销较小
for compilation to compete with your
进行编译以与您竞争
execution threads for your application
您的应用程序的执行线程
that are doing real work for you and of
正在为您和
course we're getting the space savings
当然，我们可以节省空间
the density improvements if you're
如果您要提高密度
running multiple JVMs that are running
运行多个正在运行的JVM
the same code and now we can run on on
相同的代码，现在我们可以继续
you know platforms that for whatever
你知道平台不管
reason might disallow runtime generation
原因可能会禁止运行时生成
of machine code so I have little stars
机器代码，所以我很少
next to all this so what I'm saying is
所有这些旁边，所以我的意思是
your mileage may vary and what I mean by
你的里程可能会有所不同，我的意思是
that it's like a lot of options like
这就像很多选择
like tiered compilation or different
如分层编译或其他
different GCC's garbage collectors you
不同的GCC垃圾收集器
will find that some applications benefit
会发现某些应用程序受益
from these changes and improvements and
从这些变化和改进中
other ones might even have performance
其他人甚至可能有表现
regressions from it it's very hard to
从中回归很难
say there's no silver bullet that kind
说没有那种子弹
of improves all cases and that's one of
改善了所有情况，这是其中之一
the reasons why this technology is is
这项技术之所以是
not really you know officially supported
并不是真的，您知道官方支持吗
yet and and it might be even longer
还可能更长
before it would be on by default and
才默认打开
that's because really there's there's
那是因为真的有
cases where where this actually doesn't
实际情况并非如此的情况
doesn't help but for many applications
对于许多应用程序无济于事
we've seen improvements
我们已经看到了改进
so I'm sure there's a few people in the
所以我确定里面有几个人
audience they're going you know quicker
观众他们要去，你会更快地知道
quicker warm-up times quicker startup
更快的预热时间，更快的启动
times
次
sharing data among different JVMs all
在不同的JVM之间共享数据
this sounds pretty darn familiar like
这听起来真是太熟悉了
why do I think I've heard all this
为什么我觉得我听到了所有这些
before and reality is there's actually a
之前和现实中实际上有一个
number of other pieces of functionality
其他功能数量
that have been added to the platform in
已添加到该平台的
the recent years that kind of have very
最近几年有非常
similar design goals to what we're
与我们类似的设计目标
trying to do with a ot and so I just
试图做一个OT，所以我只是
want to cover those really quickly to
想要快速覆盖那些
kind of put everything in perspective
放眼一切
and see how IOT kind of fits into the
并看看物联网如何适合
larger picture of startup time and
启动时间的大图和
performance improvements that we're
我们正在改善的性能
trying to do so the two big ones are
试图这样做，两个大的是
tiered compilation and class data
分层编译和类数据
sharing and also app class data sharing
共享以及应用程序类数据共享
and of course with the the announcement
当然还有公告
that we're basically taking all of what
我们基本上将所有
are currently the commercial features of
目前是
the JVM and making them open source for
JVM并使其成为开源
the first time open JDK users will also
第一次开放JDK的用户还将
be able to take advantage of app class
能够利用应用程序类
data sharing in the very near future so
在不久的将来进行数据共享
tiered compilation it's a pretty
分层编译非常漂亮
complicated topic and of its own so I
话题本身很复杂，所以我
don't want to dive into too much detail
不想深入细节
here but basically idea is that we no
在这里，但基本上的想法是，我们没有
longer have to make the choice between
不得不在以下两者之间做出选择
using the ce-1 compiler or the c2
使用ce-1编译器或c2
compiler we actually use both and so
编译器我们实际上同时使用了
traditionally the server JVM would just
传统上，服务器JVM只会
have the interpreter which would run for
有将要运行的口译员
say you know 15,000 executions of a
说您知道15,000次执行
particular method and then it would
特定的方法，然后它将
compile it using all the profiling data
使用所有分析数据进行编译
and with tieran enabled we now have a
启用tieran后，我们现在有了
mid-weight point where we use the c1
我们使用c1的中点
compile a compiler to generate
编译生成
instrumented code that collects the
收集代码的工具化代码
profiling data needed by c2 but also is
分析c2所需的数据，但是
much quicker and easier than a full c2
比完整的c2更快更容易
compilation so we kind of get the best
编译，以便我们获得最佳
of both worlds we get a really quick
在两个世界中，我们都能很快
compilation that happens very early on
编译发生得很早
in the life cycle of the process but
在过程的生命周期中
it's it's fast enough that it's it's
这是足够快的是
dramatically quicker than interpreting
比翻译快得多
the the Java bytecode directly and that
Java字节码直接和
kind of makes things faster until later
一种使事情更快直到后来的事情
c2 can come in and give you the real
c2可以进来给你真正的
peak perform
巅峰表现
it's a nice happy middle ground we also
这是一个很好的快乐中间地带
have a class data sharing so in a
具有班级数据共享，因此在
traditional situation this should look
传统情况应该看起来
very familiar to a few slides ago we
几张幻灯片之前我们非常熟悉
have masane class is being loaded by
masane类正在由加载
multiple JVMs on the same OS instance
同一OS实例上的多个JVM
each JVM is going to go through all the
每个JVM都要经历所有
effort of parsing the the Java bytecode
解析Java字节码的努力
and turning that into the internal data
并将其转化为内部数据
structures that are used by the hotspot
热点使用的结构
JVM traditionally those restored in the
JVM传统上是在
permanent generation now that that
现在那永久的一代
information has been moved over to what
信息已移至
we call the meta space in JDK 8 but the
我们在JDK 8中称元空间
point is is that it's consuming genuine
关键是它消耗着真正的
memory so with class data sharing the
内存，以便与类数据共享
idea is that you would create an archive
想法是，您将创建一个存档
that would sit on your file system and
那将坐在您的文件系统上，
that would actually have kind of pre
那实际上会有种
parsed or predigested versions of the
的解析或摘要版本
class data and so the JVM s could share
类数据，因此JVM可以共享
that and that would give you a faster
那会给你更快
startup time because you're not actually
启动时间，因为您实际上不是
parsing the Java bytecode and it would
解析Java字节码，它将
also give you some density improvements
也给你一些密度的改善
because you're sharing that across
因为你正在分享
multiple address spaces so there's
多个地址空间
actually two different forms of class
实际上是两种不同形式的课堂
data sharing as the the standard class
数据共享为标准类
data sharing that's been around for
一直在进行的数据共享
quite a while I'm not actually don't
相当一段时间我不是
remember when they added add something
记得他们添加时添加的东西
somewhere on the 5 or 6 era and and
在5或6时代的某个地方，以及
that's kind of free to everybody to use
每个人都可以免费使用
that's never been a commercial feature
这从来都不是商业功能
but it is only works with the JDK
但仅适用于JDK
classes themselves ie what used to be
类本身，即曾经是
part of Archie jar so the Java SC class
Archie jar的一部分，因此Java SC类
library was really the only classes that
图书馆实际上是唯一的类
were more compatible or that worked with
更兼容或与
the traditional class data sharing then
然后传统的类数据共享
there's apt class data sharing which as
有适当的类数据共享
you can probably assume from the name
你可能会假设名字
means that it's the same class data
表示它是相同的类数据
sharing technology but applied to your
分享技术，但已应用于您的
own classes and within your application
自己的类并在您的应用程序中
and so with app class data sharing you
并通过应用类数据共享给您
can actually do the same thing with your
其实可以和你做同样的事情
classes and share them across just kind
上课并分享给他们
of pre parsed versions of them across
它们之间的预解析版本
multiple JVM instances and today that
多个JVM实例，今天
this is a commercial feature that you
这是您的商业功能
don't that's not part of open JDK and
那不是开放JDK的一部分吗？
you don't you know get to use this
你不知道可以使用这个
without paying
不用付钱
Oracle money but in the future in the
甲骨文有钱但将来会
very near future
不久的将来
just with java flight recorder and all
只是与Java飞行记录器和所有
the other great stuff we're actually
实际上是其他很棒的东西
bringing this into the open source and
将其带入开源
so this would be part of open JDK in the
因此，这将是
in the very near future
在不久的将来
so just to make clear what that what the
所以只是为了弄清楚那是什么
differences here are so the reason this
这里的差异是这样的原因
whole sounds probably really familiar
整个声音可能真的很熟悉
for you is because a lot of these diet
对你来说是因为这些饮食中有很多
design goals are the same tiered
设计目标是相同的层次
compilation that the killer apps so to
杀手级应用的汇编
speak for that a faster startup time and
代表着更快的启动时间，
faster or at least a less noticeable
更快或更不明显
warmup gap and then class data sharing
预热差距，然后进行类数据共享
app class data sharing is also giving
应用类数据共享也给
you quicker warmup time and some some
您可以加快预热时间，并且一些
better memory efficiency by removing the
通过删除
redundancy that would otherwise be there
否则会存在冗余
for having multiple JVM load the same
使多个JVM加载相同
classes but what's different from all
类，但有什么不同
these what makes a OT unique is that
这些使OT独特的是
none of these involve actual the output
这些都不涉及实际的输出
of the JIT compilation process so a OT
JIT编译过程的说明，因此是OT
is all about what would be within the
就是关于
JVM code cache this is actually the
JVM代码缓存实际上是
machine code that's generated all of the
生成所有
class data sharing an app class data
类数据共享应用程序类数据
sharing saved the metadata about the
共享保存了有关
classes but it didn't it didn't actually
上课，但实际上不是
do anything with generated code so t
用生成的代码做任何事情，所以
is really a first for the platform and
确实是该平台的第一个
all of these technologies work together
所有这些技术一起工作
it's not a mutually exclusive situation
这不是相互排斥的情况
where you have to choose one over the
您必须在其中选择一个
other
其他
and we found in our performance testing
我们在性能测试中发现
that they actually really work best if
他们实际上真的工作得最好
you use all of them at the same time so
您可以同时使用所有这些
this is a ot represents another
这是一个OT代表另一个
incremental improvement in our goals of
逐步改善我们的目标
faster startup time and and better
启动时间更快，更好
memory usage so it was suggested before
内存使用情况，所以之前建议
I did the this particular talk for Java
我为Java做过这个特别的演讲
de Tokyo that I could play better
我可以打得更好的东京
humanize my presentations by having more
通过更多内容使我的演示人性化
pictures of people and I was given this
人的照片，我得到了这个
slide so this brings the total of
幻灯片，这样就带来了总计
pictures of people to 10 entire
人的照片到10整个
presentation which is a pretty good
演示文稿，这是一个很好的
average I think most most of my
平均而言，我认为大部分
co-workers have only like 5 or 6
同事只有5个或6个
pictures of people so I don't think
人的照片，所以我不认为
anyone's going to complain anymore usage
任何人都会抱怨使用不再
so this is where we get into the meat of
所以这是我们进入
things so as already mentioned we have
如前所述，我们有
this new tool J a OTC and it's sitting
这款新工具是OTC，它坐着
there just right next to Java C and
就在Java C和
everything else in your bin directory
bin目录中的其他所有内容
and using it is pretty darn simple
并且使用它非常简单
they because you have to actually
他们，因为你必须
explicitly label the output otherwise
明确标记输出，否则
you get like a really horrendous default
你会得到一个非常可怕的默认值
name well I think it's like output dot
好吧，我想这就像输出点
soo or something it kind of reminds me
o或某种让我想起的东西
of GCC but anyway you just tell it what
海湾合作委员会，但无论如何，你只是告诉它什么
the name of the library that you want to
您想要的库的名称
generate and you feed it your class and
生成并为您提供课程
it will it will give you it will give
它会给你它会给你
you that that shared object file and of
您那个共享对象文件和
course there's rather extensive online
当然，网上有很多
help that will be useful especially if
帮助将是有用的，特别是如果
it's a new tool and you'll notice if the
这是一个新工具，您会注意到
default invocation kind of follows the
默认调用类型如下
UNIX philosophy of you know don't say
您知道的UNIX哲学不说
anything unless stuff goes wrong and
除非出现问题，否则什么都不会发生
that's to be compatible with all your
与您所有的东西兼容
standard tools that assume that any
假设任何
extraneous outplay represents some sort
外来的表现代表某种
of error but you can change that with
错误，但您可以使用
the info flag and that kind of visit
信息标志和这种访问
it's like a verbose setting and it that
这就像一个冗长的设置，
will actually tell you what it what it
会告诉你它到底是什么
found in the class file and and what it
在类文件中找到了什么
decide decided to try and compile so you
决定决定尝试编译，以便您
can kind of prove to yourself that it's
可以向自己证明这是
working as you expect it to do which is
如您所愿地工作
kind of important to do the sanity
做理智很重要
checks when you're using a new tool so
检查您何时使用新工具，以便
there's there's a few gotchas that are
有一些陷阱
kind of interesting one is that by
有趣的是
assertions which most people you know
你知道大多数人的断言
never bother to enable actually has to
永远不必费心启用
be known at compile time and normally of
在编译时通常是已知的
JIT compilation this isn't an issue
JIT编译这不是问题
because the the JVM knows if you have an
因为JVM知道您是否拥有
assertion is enabled or not but one
断言是否启用，但一个
thing that could happen is if you
可能发生的事情是
compile without assertions enabled ahead
无需预先声明就可以编译
of time and then you run it in your JVM
时间，然后在JVM中运行它
you think during the runtime that just
您认为在运行时
by enabling assertions there that you're
通过在那里启用断言
getting all of your assertions turned on
打开所有的断言
when in reality anything that you
当现实中任何你
compile ahead of time with with this
与此提前编译
tool will not have the assertions
工具将没有断言
enabled so if you want to have those
启用，所以如果你想拥有那些
assertions on you have to make that
关于你的断言必须使
decision when you do the t compilation
决定何时进行äôt编译
and this flag this compile with
这个标志与此编译
assertions lets you do that I think we
断言可以让您做到这一点，我认为我们
have the compiled commands flag and this
有已编译的命令标志，这
is simply just a way to kind of bail out
只是一种纾困的方式
of compiling specific methods in the
编译特定方法的过程
future we might expand this we might add
将来我们可能会扩展它，我们可能会添加
other options or settings or whatnot but
其他选项或设置
as of today the only thing we support is
到今天为止，我们唯一支持的是
excluding individual methods
排除个别方法
or you can use wildcards to to say
或者您可以使用通配符来说
exclude an entire package and so because
排除整个包裹，所以因为
this technology is new and we haven't
这项技术是新的，我们还没有
exactly worked out all the kinks there
完全解决了那里的所有问题
are cases where you you'll have problems
在某些情况下您会遇到问题
where a particular method might cause
特定方法可能导致的地方
the t compilation itself to fail or
编译本身失败或
perhaps even worse the method might be
也许更糟糕的方法可能是
compiled but it might be compiled
已编译，但可能已编译
incorrectly and so the generated machine
错误地，因此生成的机器
code might have some sort of problem in
代码可能在其中存在某种问题
it and so at runtime that problem
它，所以在运行时出现问题
manifests in some scary way and so what
以某种可怕的方式表现出来
you can do is if you find that there's a
你可以做的是，如果发现有一个
particular method that's causing a
导致
problem well first thing is I'm hoping
问题很好，第一件事就是我希望
that you'll send us a bug report if we
如果我们将您的错误报告发送给我们
don't know about it already but the
还不知道，但是
second thing is that you can use an
第二件事是，您可以使用
exclude line in a compiled commands file
在已编译的命令文件中排除行
so you can just tell a OT to compile
这样你就可以告诉OT编译
everything but that method and then
除了那种方法，然后
continue using it so it's not just
继续使用它，不只是
classes the the kind of hello world
类的问候世界
example is just you know doing a class
例子就是你知道上课
but in practice what we usually want to
但是实际上我们通常想要
work with is either an entire module at
使用的是整个模块
a time or an entire jar file at a time
一次或一次整个jar文件
and t has no problem doing that it'll
äôt这样做毫无问题
just suck the entire thing up one thing
只是把整个事情吸了一件事
I want to point out is that compilation
我想指出的是，编译
as I've said several times already is
正如我已经说过好几次了
extremely resource intensive and Grell
非常耗费资源并且格力
which is the compiler that we use for
这是我们用于的编译器
IOT compilation definitely uses a lot of
物联网编译肯定会使用很多
a lot of memory and a lot of resources
大量的内存和大量的资源
and because this actually happens in
因为这实际上发生在
Java this is you know this is all Java
Java这就是你所知道的就是全部Java
software that does the compilation for
进行编译的软件
us this is a native code we actually
我们这是一个本地代码
have a heap that you can run out of and
有堆你可以用光了
so for example if you're compiling the
因此，例如，如果您正在编译
entire java base module
整个Java基本模块
I found recent builds that I need about
我发现了我需要的最新版本
somewhere between a five and a six
五到六点之间
gigabyte heap just two to compile Java
技嘉堆只有两个来编译Java
base so if you pass this command line
基本，所以如果您通过此命令行
today to the t compiler it'll actually
今天到äôt编译器，实际上
thrown out of memory or on most systems
内存不足或在大多数系统上
because most systems you're not going to
因为大多数系统您都不会
have a default heap maximum heap size
具有默认的堆最大堆大小
big enough to handle all this so if
大到足以应付所有这些
you're going to compile something big
你将要编译一些大东西
just be prepared and this is like you
做好准备，就像你一样
know a huge chunk of the JDK so it's not
知道JDK的很大一部分，所以它不是
that surprising but
那令人惊讶，但
be prepared to give it lots of memory
准备给它很多内存
and a lot of time I think I think this
很多时间我都认为
usually takes about somewhere between 20
通常需要大约20
and 30 minutes depending on how fast
和30分钟，具体取决于速度
your machine is it's pretty intense so
你的机器很紧张所以
another thing is that and that the
另一件事是，那个
syntax is not unique to the t compiler
语法不是äôt编译器独有的
but you should be aware how to pass
但你应该知道如何通过
options so of course like for example if
选项当然像例如
you want to set a larger maximum heap
您想要设置更大的最大堆
size this would be the way that you do
大小，这将是您的方式
it and this is the standard format that
它是这是标准格式
of a C and a whole bunch of other tools
C和一大堆其他工具
use that allow you to pass things to the
使用它可以让您将事物传递给
JVM running whatever the whatever it is
JVM运行任何东西
that the tool that you're trying to
您正在尝试的工具
execute there but this is actually way
在那里执行，但这实际上是这样
more important than then you would
比那时更重要
normally and I'm going to explain why in
通常，我将解释为什么
a few more slides but just know so it's
几张幻灯片，但只知道它是
the standard - J and then whatever
标准-J然后是其他
whatever JVM option you want to pass I
您想传递的任何JVM选项
know it's only gonna it's only going to
知道这只会下去
be what you explicitly hand it on the
是您明确将其交给
command line
命令行
it won't go behind your back and compile
它不会落后于您进行编译
anything for better or for worse so
不管是好是坏
there's another option this ties into
还有另一种选择
the tiered compilation that I would
我会分层的编译
introduced a few slides ago and there's
介绍了几张幻灯片，还有
a compiled for tiered option so it turns
编译为分层选项，因此它变成
out that you know internally the the t
知道你内部知道
tool does not use the same
工具不使用相同
implementation for compilation that the
编译的实现
hotspot JIT compilers use like I said we
像我说过的那样，热点JIT编译器使用
had to jet compiled we have C 1 and C 2
必须进行喷射编译，我们有C 1和C 2
and a lot of people assume that well
很多人都认为很好
obviously they ot tools going to use
显然，他们使用的工具
that that code base or that
该代码库或那个
implementation to compile but it
实现编译但是
actually uses growl growl which is part
实际上使用咆哮咆哮这是一部分
of the Oracle labs work and study into
Oracle实验室的工作和研究
JVM technology and growl produces code
JVM技术和咆哮产生代码
that that is uniquely different from C 1
与C 1唯一不同的地方
C 2 and performance wise it's actually
C 2和性能明智的是
somewhere in between a lot of testing
在很多测试之间的某个地方
that we've done shows that to somewhere
我们所做的表明那到某个地方
be somewhere about maybe 10 percent
大概是百分之十
slower than than C 2 which is pretty
比C 2还慢
darn good
该死的好
but you're not getting the full peak
但是你没有达到最高峰
performance that you'd get from from a
您将从中获得的效果
legitimate C to compile and probably the
合法的C进行编译，可能
missing piece there is the fact that we
缺少的部分是事实，我们
don't have the runtime profiling
没有运行时分析
information that c2 can take advantage
c2可以利用的信息
of when it JIT compiler stuff so the
JIT编译器的时间，所以
actual ideal situation for for peak
高峰的实际理想情况
performance is as I said earlier to use
性能是我之前说过的
t as just one component in your
只是您的一个组成部分
strategy for getting the best
最佳策略
performance possible and you do that by
性能可能，您可以通过
saying compile four-tiered when you have
如果有的话说编译四层
ot compile and so what that does is it
OT编译，那么它是做什么的
doesn't generate the default growl code
不生成默认的咆哮代码
it tells growl to include the the
它告诉咆哮包括
profiling instrumentation that c2
c2的分析仪器
requires for it to compile so you
需要它来编译，所以你
actually end up with the same kind of
实际上以相同的方式结束
scenario that you do of tiered
您分层的情况
compilation except the the middle step
除中间步骤外的编译
is no longer c1 it's the the t
不再是c1，而是äôt
compiled growl code and that will be
编译的咆哮代码，这将是
just a precursor to what will hopefully
只是希望的前兆
eventually be the c2 compiled code and
最终是c2编译的代码，
so you don't have to you basically get
所以你基本上不需要
to have your cake and eat it too
还要吃你的蛋糕
here as well you get the the immediate
在这里，您也可以立即获得
performance advantage right out of the
性能优势
gate of having a pre compiled code there
那里有预编译代码的大门
but then eventually the JVM on its own
但是最终，JVM自行产生了
time can can loop around and see to it
时间可以环顾四周
to give you that extra 10% bump so what
给你额外的10％的颠簸
does actually do when you run it when it
确实在您运行它时执行
when actually first proposed to this
当实际上第一次提出这个建议时
talk I was like well we're going to do a
谈话我感觉很好，我们将要做一个
whole bunch of demos and it turns out
整个演示，结果
the demos are like not horribly exciting
演示就像不令人兴奋
because well this is it works right and
因为这是正确的，并且
there's nothing here that would tell you
这里没有什么可以告诉你的
that you know the library that you
你知道你的图书馆
actually created was used so what can we
使用实际创建的，所以我们能做什么
do if we actually want to verify that
如果我们确实要验证
that was actually used well there's an
实际上使用得很好，有一个
option there's a new option that's been
选项，有一个新的选择
added to the JVM called print t and
添加到名为printäôt的JVM和
it's disabled by default obviously but
默认情况下它是默认禁用的，但是
if you put that in and you run it you'll
如果您将其放入并运行它，您将
actually get some output that's going to
实际得到一些输出
look a little similar to the print
看起来有点像印刷品
compilation output that we're all pretty
我们都很漂亮的编译输出
used to seeing and this is telling you
曾经看到，这告诉你
two important pieces of information here
这里的两个重要信息
one that it was able to find the library
一个能够找到图书馆的人
and load it
并加载它
and the other two things is that there
另外两件事是
were two separate methods that were
是两种不同的方法
identified and loaded into or kind of
确定并装入或种类
acknowledged as being part of the code
被确认为代码的一部分
cache and that's the constructor for the
缓存，这就是
class and then the actual hello world
课，然后是实际的世界
main which you guys don't need to see
你们不需要看的主要
the source code for because it's as
源代码，因为它是
boring as you're imagining so let's look
像您想象的那样无聊，让我们来看一下
at let's try the same thing so let's go
让我们尝试相同的事情，让我们开始吧
and I'm gonna disable compressed
我将禁用压缩
oops so just just to get an idea how
哎呀，所以只是为了了解如何
many people here are familiar with
这里很多人都熟悉
compressed oops compressed references
压缩oop压缩引用
okay so about two thirds so good we're
好吧，大约三分之二这么好，我们
I'm gonna go into a little bit of detail
我要详细一点
time permitting a bit later in the slide
时间允许稍晚一点在幻灯片中
deck about those but you know very
甲板上那些，但你知道的很
common thing is is that you might want
常见的是您可能想要
to you know disable compressed
你知道禁用压缩
references for compressed oops
压缩oops参考
for whatever reason so here we're
无论出于什么原因，我们在这里
starting the JVM and I'm just disabling
启动JVM，我只是禁用
that and everything else is just like it
那和其他一切都一样
was on the command line earlier and
之前在命令行上
you'll see that I actually get an error
您会看到我实际上收到了一个错误
it tells me that hey you know you you
它告诉我，嘿，你认识你，你
wanted to load this t library but it's
想加载这个äôt库，但是
actually was compiled with different
实际上是用不同的方式编译的
settings than what the JVM runtime is
设置，而不是JVM运行时
set for now notice it does actually run
现在设置，请注意它确实在运行
the code nothing actually broke so even
该代码实际上没有中断，所以甚至
when we fail to load the t library and
当我们无法加载äôt库和
use it for whatever reason your
出于任何原因使用它
application will still rotten you'll
应用程序仍然会烂掉
just get a little warning if you have
只要有一点警告
the print t if you don't have the
如果您没有
print t listed it'll actually silently
打印出来，它实际上会默默地
fail to load the AOA ot library which
无法加载AOA ot库
may or may not be the ideal behavior but
可能是理想的行为，也可能不是
it does kind of follow along
它确实遵循
the philosophy of not breaking anything
不破坏任何东西的哲学
that currently works so the idea here is
目前有效，所以这里的想法是
that you need to match your your runtime
您需要匹配您的运行时
with the compilation so the options that
与编译，所以选项
you use during compilation have to match
您在编译期间使用的必须匹配
the options that use during the runtime
运行时使用的选项
and here I'm just pointing out that if
这里我只是指出，如果
you if you took away I'm reiterating
你，如果你带走，我重申
basically that if you take away the
基本上，如果您拿走
print t thing and you run it this is
打印东西，然后运行它，这是
still failing this is exactly the same
仍然失败，这是完全一样的
command line that I was just passing
我刚刚通过的命令行
except we don't have the verbosity
除了我们没有冗长
output and so it's silently failing to
输出，所以它默默地失败了
load that for you but we have to we have
为您加载，但我们必须拥有
to match these these options and the the
匹配这些选项和
current kind of documentation so to
当前的文档类型
speak the the JEP document which is the
说出JEP文件，即
closest thing we have to to any kind of
我们必须面对的最接近的事物
official documentation for a OT
OT的官方文件
currently says it just simply says that
目前说只是说
you need to match the options but it
您需要匹配选项，但是
doesn't really say which options you you
并没有真正说出您的选择
really need to to match although it's
确实需要匹配，尽管
implied and in practice there's only two
暗示，实际上只有两个
things you need to worry about you need
您需要担心的事情
to worry about which garbage collector
担心哪个垃圾收集器
you're using and you need to worry about
您正在使用，您需要担心
whether compressed oops is enabled or
是否启用压缩的oop或
not and it's kind of interesting the
没有，这很有趣
thing about why that's the case but just
关于为什么这样的事情，但仅仅是
to summarize here so you can think of
在这里总结，以便您可以想到
every single compile t compile and
每个单独的编译-编译
every single run as falling into one of
每一次运行都属于
these four quadrants so you know each of
这四个象限，所以您知道每个
these is can just be thought of as a
这些可以被认为是一个
binary thing and it's either on or off
二进制的东西，它要么开要么关
and I'll give I'll stick you into one of
我会给你，让你坚持其中之一
these things so as long as you match
这些东西，只要你匹配
your a ot compile with your runtime
您的运行时编译
settings then the library should be
设置，那么库应该是
loaded and we make sure that that it's
加载，我们确保它是
sanity checks it when it loads the
健全性在加载时检查
library so that you don't ever end up
库，这样您就永远不会结束
loading something that is incompatible
加载不兼容的东西
with the runtime additionally we also of
通过运行时，我们还可以
course check that the class hasn't
当然要检查课程没有
changed so there's code in there that
改变了，所以里面有代码
basically fingerprints classes that this
基本上是指纹类
isn't we don't really intend for like
不是我们不是真的想要
malicious users to try and do anything
恶意用户尝试做任何事情
sneaky so it's not like a cryptographic
偷偷摸摸的，所以它不像加密
sound hash or anything like that but it
声音哈希或类似的东西，但它
should be enough to prevent you from
应该足以防止您
accidentally making a change to your
意外地更改了您的
class so the bytecode doesn't match the
类，因此字节码与
the library that was produced from a ot
从一个OT产生的库
compilation of that same bytecode so why
相同字节码的编译，为什么
do we need to synchronize VM options
我们需要同步VM选项吗
that seems like a really arbitrary kind
看起来真的很武断
of pain in the body dang right like that
身体的疼痛就这样晃来晃去
it's a usability issue and there
这是一个可用性问题
certainly is room for improvement here
这里肯定有改进的空间
and that is kind of on the internal
这在内部
roadmap to hopefully make this work a
希望使这项工作成为一个路线图
little bit easier or better or at least
一点点容易或更美好或更至少
be a little more intuitive but today you
多一点直觉，但今天你
you really can't do what we referred to
你真的做不到我们所说的
as cross compilation and what I mean by
作为交叉编译，我的意思是
cross compilation is I'm not talking
交叉编译不是我在说
about from one CPU type to another but
从一种CPU类型到另一种
even
甚至
like from we've compressed references
就像我们压缩了参考文献一样
using a JVM running the OT tool that
使用运行OT工具的JVM
uses compressed references to a runtime
使用对运行时的压缩引用
that doesn't use compressed references
不使用压缩参考
we don't currently support that so why
我们目前不支持，为什么
don't we support that well if we look at
如果我们看一下我们不是很好地支持
the compressed referent or compressed
压缩的参考对象或压缩的
oops and oops oops by the way is
哎呀哎呀哎呀
everyone familiar with the term oops sir
熟悉oops先生的每个人
okay so oops just means a reference it's
好的，哎呀，仅表示参考
a pointer to an object on the heap that
指向堆上对象的指针
it stands for ordinary object pointer
它代表普通的对象指针
and it's kind of a strange name but it
这是一个奇怪的名字，但是
has a lot of historical precedent so
有很多历史先例
small talk and self apparently used this
闲聊和自我显然使用了这个
term and and that's why we've inherited
学期，这就是为什么我们继承了
it and of course the hotspot JVM kind of
它，当然还有热点JVM
evolved from a self runtime so there's a
是从自我运行时演变而来的
lot of history there for free using that
免费使用那里的很多历史
term but we knew here oops just think of
学期，但我们知道在这里，小伙子们会想到
object reference it's it's a pointer
对象引用是一个指针
into the heap somewhere so compressed
到堆里这样压缩的地方
oops is well a compressed object pointer
oops是一个压缩的对象指针
of some kind so what the idea is is that
这样的想法是
originally when you make when we made
最初当你创造的时候
the move from 32-bit to 64-bit there was
从32位迁移到64位
a performance penalty that you were
你曾经表现欠佳
paying even on a platform like Intel
甚至在像Intel这样的平台上付款
where you were getting all these
你在哪里得到所有这些
additional registers and stuff and so
额外的寄存器和东西等等
you'd normally expect kind of a speed-up
您通常会期望加速
when you go to 64 bit because the
当您转到64位，因为
register pressure was relieved to a
寄存器压力释放到
great extent but the slowdown was a
在很大程度上，但放缓是
result of the fact that all of a sudden
突然之间事实的结果
all of our references are 64-bit and of
我们所有的参考资料都是64位的
course this isn't Java specific I mean
当然这不是Java特有的
all software kind of has the same
所有软件都具有相同的
problem when you move from 32-bit to
从32位迁移到
64-bit is that all of a sudden you you
64位是突然之间你
you have this bandwidth cost between
您的带宽成本介于
memory and the CPU because all of the
内存和CPU，因为所有
pointers are now twice as big so for the
指针的大小现在是指针的两倍大
heap maybe we could do something to
堆，也许我们可以做点什么
alleviate that overhead and to kind of
减轻开销，并减轻
make that regression just magically go
使回归变得神奇
away and the cool thing is the the guys
离开，最酷的是这些家伙
that son did find a way to do this and
那个儿子确实找到了办法
actually actually I think we did this a
实际上我认为我们做到了
j-rok at first and they copied us but
首先是j-rok，他们抄袭了我们，但
I'm not entirely sure what the history
我不确定是什么历史
of there is but um anyway maybe maybe we
那里，但是无论如何，也许我们
both came up with the idea at the same
两者都提出了相同的想法
time but the idea is pretty simple it's
时间，但想法很简单，
what is is if the heap is actually
如果堆实际上是什么
smaller than four gigabytes
小于4 GB
then you don't need a heap address space
那么您就不需要堆地址空间
that's larger than 32 bits so what you
大于32位，所以你
can do is just you know stick the heap
可以做的就是知道堆在上面
somewhere in your address in the
在您地址中的某处
processes address space and then just
处理地址空间，然后
add the offset of wherever that heap
添加该堆的偏移量
starts to every he preference and oh you
开始每个他的喜好，哦，你
basically can address an entire four
基本上可以解决整个四个
gigabyte of heap without having to store
无需存储的千兆字节堆
64 bits of every address and this has a
每个地址的64位，这有一个
tremendous impact on the performance not
对性能的巨大影响不是
just of speed but of size because all of
只是速度而大小，因为所有
your objects any object that has a lot
您的物体任何具有很多物体的物体
of references in it to other objects
对其他对象的引用
pointers to other objects become
指向其他对象的指针变为
significantly smaller so it can actually
小得多，所以它实际上可以
make your heap consumption smaller as
使您的堆消耗较小
well so this is great
好，这很好
but how does this actually get
但这实际上是如何得到的
implemented well I said there's you know
实施得很好我说你知道
we break the 64 bit pointer into kind of
我们将64位指针分解为
two halves and so there's a 32 bit least
两半，所以至少有32位
significant bits and then there's 32 bit
有效位，然后是32位
most significant bits and the idea is
最重要的部分，这个想法是
that this these are not going to change
这些不会改变的
right if you have a heap that's under
对，如果你有一个堆在下面
four gigabytes and you align it
4 GB，您将其对齐
correctly so it's not sitting on on a
正确，所以它不是坐在一个
border between two different you know
你知道两个不同的边界
kind of 32-bit address space pages in a
一种32位地址空间页
sense then this whole this will be the
感觉那么整个这将是
same for all of your pointers and so we
您的所有指针都一样，所以我们
can just like throw that away we don't
可以像扔掉我们一样
need to keep that information handy and
需要保持信息方便
so this is what actually gets stored in
所以这实际上是存储在
every field of an object on the heap
堆上对象的每个字段
that's pointing to another object and
指向另一个对象
that's all fine and dandy but then how
很好，很花花公子，但是那怎么
do we actually use that and so in the
我们实际使用了那个，所以在
code that's generated when we're
当我们
actually looking at a reference because
实际上在看参考，因为
obviously on the 64-bit platform if we
显然，如果我们在64位平台上
have a pointer that's in a register on
有一个指针在寄存器中
the CPU or somewhere in in this the
CPU或其中的某处
threads execution stack it has to be a
线程执行栈必须是
real 64-bit pointer right so how do we
真正的64位指针正确，那么我们该怎么办
expand it or uncompress it and basically
展开或解压缩，基本上
all we do is just we add the the base
我们要做的就是添加基础
address of the heap to it so it's very
堆的地址，所以它非常
simple and really easy but it's
简单，真的很容易，但是
something that we have to do and
我们必须要做的事情
compiled code has to do this so this is
编译的代码必须这样做，所以这是
one we have to know ahead of time when
我们必须提前知道的时候
we t compile that this is actually
我们编译这实际上是
pointing you know this is actually
指出你知道这实际上是
compressed reference not a full
压缩参考不完整
reference and then we have to actually
参考，然后我们必须实际
manipulate it but
操纵它，但是
or we can use it in its raw form this
或者我们可以以原始形式使用它
really cheap and easy to do but a more
真正便宜又容易做，但是更多
complicated example is what if the heap
复杂的例子是如果堆
is somewhere between 4 and 32 gigabytes
在4到32 GB之间
well surprisingly we can actually do
令人惊讶的是，我们实际上可以做到
compressed references they are too and
压缩的引用他们也是
the trick is that on a 64-bit platform
诀窍是在64位平台上
there's alignment requirements right so
有对齐要求，所以
we have to basically start everything at
我们必须从根本上开始一切
a multiple of 8 the address always has
地址始终具有8的倍数
to be a multiple of 8 and so that means
是8的倍数，所以这意味着
that in the address the least
至少在地址中
significant 3 bits are always going to
有效的3位总是
be 0 which means of course if it's in
为0，这当然意味着
variate that that that's redundant
认为那是多余的
information we don't need that so that
我们不需要的信息
kind of expands our are the ability of
一种扩展我们的能力
the largest amount of address space that
最大的地址空间
we can reason about to 8 times what it
我们可以推理到它的8倍
was before so that gives us actually a
之前，所以实际上给了我们
32 gigabyte chunk of space that that we
我们占用了32 GB的空间
can reference with just 32 unique beds
只能参考32张独特的床
and so we just kind of take that out
所以我们只是拿出来
then you know the kind of the only part
那么你知道那唯一的部分
that matters so to speak and this is
可以这么说，这是
what gets stored in the heap and then
什么存储在堆中，然后
everything else we sort of just throw
我们所扔的所有其他东西
away but again there's there's a cost to
离开，但同样有代价
this not so much in performance at run
在运行中没有太多的表现
time but but in complexity so when we
时间，但是很复杂，所以当我们
compile now we need to be aware that not
现在进行编译，我们需要意识到
only do we have to add some some base
我们只需要添加一些基础
address where the heap is located but we
地址堆所在的地址，但是我们
also have to shift the the address three
还得把地址移三
three digits three binary digits to the
三位数三位数
left or right depending on if we're
向左还是向右取决于我们是
compressing or uncompressing the
压缩或解压缩
reference interestingly enough this has
有趣的是，这有
this shift is basically free because the
这种转变基本上是免费的，因为
the CPUs we support allow for move
我们支持的CPU允许移动
instructions there's a scaling factor
说明有一个比例因子
that's built into the instruction so we
这是指令中内置的，所以我们
can go up to we can multiply by up to
可以上升到我们可以乘以
eight when we do these moves and so
八，当我们做这些动作，等等
there isn't actually a shift instruction
实际上没有换班指令
that's added to the outputted code it's
被添加到输出代码中
all compact and in the same move
紧凑而一致
instruction so we get this for free but
说明，所以我们免费获得
the t compiler has to be aware of it
äôt编译器必须意识到这一点
it has to
它必须
to do this and this is why we have to
为此，这就是为什么我们必须
match our or VM options the other thing
匹配我们的或VM选项
is is garbage collection strategy now
现在是垃圾回收策略
garbage collection is a huge topic with
垃圾收集是一个巨大的话题
a bunch of very complicated details very
一堆非常复杂的细节
you know none of which we really have
你不知道我们真的没有
the time to cover but just to give one
时间涵盖，但只给一个
example of why you need to be aware of
为什么需要注意的示例
what garbage collector is going to be
什么是垃圾收集器
used when you you when you are compiling
在编译时使用
for it whether it's chicken pot
为此它是否是鸡肉锅
compilation or IOT compilation is the
编译或物联网编译是
the necessity of right barriers so right
正确设置障碍的必要性
barriers are basically a way that we can
障碍基本上是我们可以
use to avoid having to do mark for the
用于避免为标记做标记
entire heap and when I say mark I'm
整个堆，当我说马克的时候
talking about mark as in mark-and-sweep
谈论标记为“扫一扫”
woman mm we want to look at the heap
女人mm，我们想看看堆
only I want to identify which objects
我只想确定哪些对象
are live versus which ones are dead
是活着还是死了
obviously for a very long time we've
显然，很长一段时间以来
used a technique called generational
使用了一种称为世代的技术
garbage collection based off of the
垃圾收集基于
generational hypothesis and that's where
世代假设，那就是
we divide the heap into an area where
我们将堆分成一个区域
it's young and then there's old and I'm
年轻，然后老，我
deliberately simplifying this
故意简化
dramatically obviously g1 looks nothing
显然，g1看起来一无所有
like this and not even CMS or anything
就像这样，甚至没有CMS之类的东西
you know there's scavenger spaces and
你知道那里有拾荒空间
and the role implementation is much more
角色执行更多
complicated but in general sometimes we
复杂，但总的来说，有时我们
have parts of the heap that we care
有我们关心的堆部分
about that we want to collect and you
关于我们想要收集的信息，您
know I'm very frequent we have other
知道我很频繁，我们还有其他
parts of the heap that we don't
我们不堆的部分
necessarily want to have to collect or
一定要收集或
mark very frequently and so we have we
经常标记，所以我们有
have some division we want to handle
我们要处理一些分歧
them differently so if I come in and I'm
他们不同，所以如果我进来，我
trying to do some sort of concurrent
试图做某种并发
collection for example and I'm you know
例如收藏，我知道
an executioner mutator thread comes in
execution子手mutator线程进来
and creates a new object and then has a
并创建一个新对象，然后有一个
and then modifies some field of some
然后修改一些
other preexisting object on the heap to
堆上其他先前存在的对象
point to this new object
指向这个新对象
well this is okay and we don't really
好吧，这还可以，我们不是真的
need to keep track of this because if
需要保持跟踪，因为如果
this is the the young space of a new
这是新事物的年轻空间
space of the nursery or whatever it is
托儿所的空间或其他
in the actual garbage collector we're
在实际的垃圾收集器中
using we're gonna find this when we mark
使用我们会在标记时找到它
this area so this is a this is actually
这个区域，所以这实际上是一个
you know fine in and of itself but what
你本身就很好，但是什么
if we have something in the old space or
如果我们在旧空间有东西，或者
you know whatever region that we don't
你知道我们不知道的任何地区
want to have to mark you know this is at
想要标记您知道这是在
the part of the heap that we don't
我们没有的堆的一部分
frequently go in and try and collect
经常去尝试收集
well if
好吧，如果
the code modifies an address pointer or
该代码修改了地址指针或
an OOP that's here in the non collected
一个非收集中的OOP
the the region we're not going to
我们不打算去的地区
collect next we need to keep track of
接下来收集我们需要跟踪
this somehow we need to do bookkeeping
我们需要以某种方式进行簿记
and so what we do is we have something
所以我们要做的是
called a card table and a card table is
叫做卡表，而卡表是
basically the data structure it's used
基本上是它使用的数据结构
for our write barriers so what is the
对于我们的写障碍，那么什么是
write barrier a write barrier is
写障碍写障碍
additional code that we admit when we
我们在我们接受的其他代码
JIT compile or that the interpreter
JIT编译或解释器
executes that says that if you if you
执行说，如果你，如果你
write to something on the heap if you
如果您在堆上写东西
change an address anywhere on the heap
在堆上的任何地方更改地址
you want to mark a little bit in this
您想在此做一点标记
card table somewhere to say hey there's
卡表某处说嘿
a change here so each little chunk of
这里有一个变化，所以每个小块
the card table is just basically like a
牌桌基本上就像一个
map that corresponds to as it happens to
恰好对应于的地图
be 512 bytes of of the heap and so if
是堆的512字节，所以如果
there's a since each of these can be
有一个，因为每个
thought of as a flag if that flag is set
如果已设置该标志，则视为标志
that tells the garbage collector that
告诉垃圾收集器
hey there was a change you know whatever
嘿，有变化，你知道
chunk of the heap corresponds to this
堆的大块与此对应
one flag there was a change there and
一个标志那里发生了变化，
you should go look at that
你应该去看看
so now when we modify any object aught
所以现在当我们修改任何对象时
you know any object field or pointer
你知道任何对象字段或指针
field in an object we just mark that
我们只标记对象中的字段
there and then here and the not young we
在那里，然后在这里，不是年轻的我们
mark that there - and then when we do a
标记在那里-然后当我们做一个
GC we can you know do the young
GC我们可以知道年轻吗
collection like we always would and you
我们一如既往的收藏
know mark the entire thing and then we
知道标记整个事情，然后我们
can just check the the individual pieces
可以检查单个零件
of the part that we're not collecting to
我们没有收集到的部分
see if there's any incoming pointers and
看看是否有任何传入的指针和
this is tremendously faster than having
这比拥有
to mark the entire thing so that's in a
标记整个东西，所以在
nutshell how we do generational
简而言之，我们如何代代相传
collection and it's also how we do
收集，这也是我们的工作方式
concurrent collection at the card table
卡表上的并发收集
the right barriers in the card table are
牌桌上正确的障碍是
integral to both of those parts of the
这两个部分不可分割的一部分
GC and I think knowing that now it's
GC，我想知道现在
pretty easy to understand that when we a
很容易理解，当我们
OT compile classes they ot compiler
OT编译器编译的类
needs to know what garbage collection
需要知道什么垃圾收集
algorithm we're using because we need to
我们正在使用的算法，因为我们需要
know whether right barriers would be
知道是否会有正确的障碍
necessary or not if you're using
如果您正在使用，则是否需要
parallel GC we actually don't need the
并行GC我们实际上不需要
right barriers necessarily you know if
正确的障碍一定知道
it was if it was not
如果不是
generational collector it's not the I
世代收藏家不是我
mean there's some cases where we didn't
意味着在某些情况下我们没有
we need different types of right barrier
我们需要不同类型的右路障碍
there's different data structures that
有不同的数据结构
the GC uses that do or do not need to be
GC使用需要或不需要
updated and you know it all depends on
更新，您知道这一切都取决于
the individual garbage collector that
各个垃圾收集器
you're using but the key takeaway is is
您正在使用，但关键要点是
that we need to know what the garbage
我们需要知道什么垃圾
collectors expectations are but when we
收藏家的期望是，但是当我们
compile so anyway we have these four
编译，无论如何，我们有这四个
different kind of scenarios or four
一类或四种不同的方案
different types of t compilation that
不同类型的äôt编译
we can end up with as a result and each
我们最终可以得到结果，每个
one corresponds to a set of GART a
一个对应于一组GART
choice of garbage collector and
选择垃圾收集器和
compressed
压缩的
oops is enabled or not enabled and
oops已启用或未启用，并且
there's a there's actually a known
实际上有一个已知的
library names that if we stick these
库名称，如果我们坚持这些
these libraries under the Lib directory
这些库在Lib目录下
of our JDK directory the the JVM runtime
JDK目录中的JVM运行时
will actually find these automatically
实际上会自动找到这些
and use them but it's only for a small
并使用它们，但这仅适用于一小部分
subset of logic modules that are
逻辑模块的子集
actually part of the JDK proper itself
实际上是JDK本身的一部分
right now so if you want to use your own
现在，如果您想使用自己的
you know if you want a OT compile your
你知道你要不要OT编译
own classes the only option you have
自己上课是您唯一的选择
today is to pass then the library file
今天要传递的是库文件
name on the command line but if you are
在命令行上命名，但如果您是
doing one of the one a chunk of the JDK
做一个JDK的一部分
itself a module from within the JDK
本身就是JDK中的一个模块
itself and it's one of these five
本身，这是这五个之一
packages or I'm sorry about one of these
包裹，或者我很抱歉其中一个包裹
five modules one of these four or Java
这四个模块之一或Java的五个模块
base if it's one of those five then you
如果是这五种之一，那么您
can just stick it in library in the libs
可以将其粘贴到库中的库中
directory and the the JVM may pick it up
目录，JVM可能会选择它
automatically so we're out of time but
自动，所以我们没时间了，但是
just to wrap things up so the value that
只是把东西包起来，这样的价值
that is added by ot compilation here is
ot编译在这里添加的是
that it really gives you a faster start
它确实为您提供了更快的开始
up you reach peak performance quicker
更快地达到最佳性能
you have a smaller footprint if you have
如果您有一个较小的足迹
multiple JVM a smaller total footprint
多个JVM，总占地面积较小
if you have multiple JVMs running the
如果您有多个JVM运行
same code and we can even run on on
相同的代码，我们甚至可以继续
platforms that would otherwise disallow
否则将不允许的平台
jet the risks here the the caveats are
在这里喷射风险，需要注意的是
that it's experimental it's not
这是实验性的，不是
documented
记录
it only runs on Linux amd64 today and
它今天只能在Linux amd64上运行，并且
custom class loaders invokedynamic or
自定义类加载器invokedynamic或
india are not supported and of course
印度不受支持，当然
your mileage may vary so there's other
您的里程可能会有所不同，因此其他
t sessions this was this one was the
会议是这个
introduction one this one was just how
介绍一，这是怎么一回事
to use it whether you know the
使用它，无论您是否知道
information you would need to consider
您需要考虑的信息
whether you might want to use it or not
您是否想要使用它
to make that decision and hopefully
做出决定并希望
you'll walk out of here with feeling
你会带着感觉离开这里
that you've learned that but if you want
你已经知道了，但是如果你想
a more in-depth talk I'll look under the
我将在下面更深入的讨论
hood
引擎盖
these guys are doing a talk from that
这些家伙正在做一个演讲
they also delivered at the JVM language
他们还以JVM语言交付
summit and this was this was excellent
首脑会议，这是很棒的
at the language summit you can actually
在语言峰会上，您实际上可以
catch it on on YouTube if you are unable
如果您无法在YouTube上捕捉到它
to see it live today but if you can fit
去看今天的直播，但是如果你能适应的话
it into your schedule I strongly suggest
我强烈建议将其纳入您的日程安排
going and seeing them live tomorrow and
去看他们明天的生活
then also there's another session I
然后还有另一个会议
don't really know the details about but
真的不知道有关的细节，但是
someone is doing a kind of more I guess
我猜有人正在做更多的事情
fundamental talk about about some of the
从根本上讲一些
principles involved with static versus a
静态与静态有关的原理
ot compilation so it should be an
OT编译，所以它应该是
interesting talk so thank you very much
有趣的谈话，非常感谢
for your time I very much appreciate the
在您的时间里，我非常感谢
oh sorry oh it's your talk okay Wow yeah
哦，抱歉，这是你的话题，好的
yeah so I'm sure it's gonna be a great
是的，所以我敢肯定这会很棒
talk okay thank you very much for your
说话好吧，非常感谢你的
time
时间
[Applause]
[掌声]